A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller, Jr. family photographs, Series 1005 FA449
Rockefeller Archive Center
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. family photographs, 1005
  - Oversized, 1890-1967; 10 Cubic Feet; Approximately 800 prints
    - Group Portraits - Family and Friends, 1896-1910; 4 prints (Box O 22)
    - Homes - Seal Harbor - Eyrie Oriental Garden, 36 contact prints (Box O 8)
    - Homes - 10 West 54th Street, 1925; 6 prints (Box O 8)
    - Homes - 740 Park Avenue, 2 prints (Box O 8)
    - Homes - 740 Park Avenue - Porcelain Collection, 10 prints (Box O 9)
    - JDR Jr - Brown University, 1890s-1937; 8 prints (Box O 10)
    - JDR Jr - Business, 1 print (Box O 22)
    - JDR Jr - Business - Industrial Labor Conference, 1919 (Box C 3)
    - JDR Jr - Business - Real Estate Interests, 4 prints (Box O 23)
    - JDR Jr - Business - Real Estate Interests, 14 prints (Box O 24)
    - JDR Jr - Business - Real Estate Interests, 12 prints (Box O 25)
    - JDR Jr - Informals, 1913, 1925; 2 prints (Box O 22)
    - JDR Jr - Miscellaneous, 1 print (Box O 22)
    - JDR Jr - Paintings (Box C 8)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies, 2 prints (Box O 17)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies, 6 prints (Box O 27)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - "A Contribution to the Heritage of Every Man", 76 prints (Box O 26)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Acadia National Park, 7 prints (Box O 17)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Agora, Bronze Plaque, Athens, Greece (Box C 2)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Agora, Athens, Greece (Box C 6)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Cathedral of St. John the Divine, 3 prints (Box O 27)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - The Cloisters, 2 prints (Box O 27)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Interchurch World Movement, 1956-1957 (Box O 28)
      Reports
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Jerusalem Museum, 6 prints (Box O 29)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 3 prints (Box O 29)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Park Avenue Baptist Church, 1923; 5 prints (Box O 29)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1 print (Box O 17)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Riverside Church, 1 print (Box O 17)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Riverside Church, 4 prints (Box O 18)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Sleepy Hollow Restorations, 1955; 1 print (Box O 30)
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - United Nations (Box C 7)
      with signature of Wally Harrison, Architect.
    - JDR Jr - Philanthropies - Williamsburg, 1943-1957; 3 prints (Box O 30)
    - JDR Jr - Portraits, 1932; 1 sketch (Box O 17)
      Sketch of JDR Jr. used for cover of Forbes magazine
    - JDR Jr - Portraits, 6 prints (Box O 19)
    - JDR Jr - Portraits, 11 prints (Box O 31)
      Including 1961 coin of JRD Jr.
    - JDR Jr - Portraits, 12 prints (Box O 32)
    - JDR Jr - Portraits, 1932-1961; 11 prints including duplicates (Box O 33)
    - JDR Jr - Portraits (Box C 7)
    - JDR Jr - Travel - China, 1921; 156 prints (Box O 11)
    - JDR Jr - Travel - China, 1921; 180 prints plus postcards. (Box O 12)
    - JDR Jr - Travel - China, 26 prints (Box O 34)
    - JDR Jr - Travel - Japan, 4 prints (Box O 17)
    - JDR Jr - Travel - Japan (Box C 8)
    - Martha Baird Rockefeller - Portraits, 6 prints (Box O 19)
    - Martha Baird Rockefeller (Box O 35)
    - Relatives - Aldrich family - Homes (Box O 20)
    - Relatives - Aldrich family, 2 prints (Box O 22)
    - Relatives - Aldrich family (Box C 4)
    - Relatives - Aldrich family (Box C 8)
    - Relatives - Aldrich family - Group Portraits, 4 glass plate negatives (Box O 37)
      Restricted - Preservation concerns
    - JDR Jr family (Box O 21)
    - JDR Jr family (Box C 5)
  - Lantern Slides, 3.87 Cubic Feet 43 boxes; Approximately 2,150 lantern slides.
    - Airplane View of Lower New York, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 36)
    - China - Great Wall, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 9)
    - China - Mukden - Tombs and Palace, Lantern Slides-33 (Box L 11)
    - China - Peking, Lantern Slides-89 total (Box L 7)
    - China - Peking, Lantern Slides-89 total (Box L 8)
    - China - Peking - Ming Tombs, Lantern Slides-20 (Box L 11)
    - China - Scenes, Lantern Slides-68 total (Box L 2)
    - China - Scenes, Lantern Slides-68 total (Box L 10)
    - Egypt - Karnak, Lantern Slides-53 (Box L 24)
    - Egypt - Memphis (Box L 37)
    - Egypt - Esna (Box L 37)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Colossi of Memon, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 26)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Medinet Habout, Lantern Slides-23 (Box L 26)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Ramesseum, Lantern Slides-11 total (Box L 26)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Ramesseum, Lantern Slides-11 total (Box L 27)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Temple of Deir el Bahri, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 26)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Temple of Korna, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 27)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Amenhotep II, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 27)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Khaemhet, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 25)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Menna, Lantern Slides-10 (Box L 27)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Nekht, Lantern Slides-8 (Box L 25)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Prince Amenkhepeshf, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 27)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Queen Nefertari, Lantern Slides-21 (Box L 26)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Ramose, Lantern Slides-8 Lantern Slides-10 (Box L 25)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Sennefer, Lantern Slides-10 (Box L 25)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Sen-Nezen, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 25)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Seti I, Lantern Slides-7 (Box L 25)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Unknown, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 25)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Tomb of Userhat, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 25)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Valley of the Kings, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 25)
    - Egypt - Thebes - Various Tombs, Lantern Slides-11 (Box L 27)
    - England - Bath - Roman Baths, Lantern Slides-7 (Box L 15)
    - England - Bath - Views, Lantern Slides-11 (Box L 15)
    - England - Cheddar - Gough's Cave, Lantern Slides-11 (Box L 15)
    - England - Chester, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 15)
    - England - Glastonbury - Glastonbury Abby, Lantern Slides-6 (Box L 14)
    - England - Haddon Hall, Lantern Slides-9 (Box L 15)
    - England - Hampton Court, Lantern Slides-26 (Box L 16)
    - England - Kenilworth Castle, Lantern Slides-8 (Box L 14)
    - England - London, Lantern Slides-11 (Box L 13)
    - England - London - Tower, Lantern Slides-12 (Box L 13)
    - England - Ludlow, Lantern Slides-14 (Box L 14)
    - England - Rowsley - Peacock Inn, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 15)
    - England - Salisbury - Salisbury Cathedral - Exteriors, Lantern Slides-9 (Box L 12)
    - England - Salisbury - Salisbury Cathedral - Interiors, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 12)
    - England - Stokesay Castle, Lantern Slides-9 (Box L 15)
    - England - Stonehenge, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 15)
    - England - Stratford, Lantern Slides-7 (Box L 14)
    - England - Stratford - Anne Hathaway's Cottage, Lantern Slides-8 (Box L 14)
    - England - Warwick Castle, Lantern Slides-16 (Box L 13)
    - England - Wells - Wells Cathedral - Exteriors, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 12)
    - England - Wells - Wells Cathedral - Interiors, Lantern Slides-9 (Box L 12)
    - England - Wilton House, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 15)
    - England - Winchester - Winchester Cathedral - Exteriors, Lantern Slides-9 (Box L 12)
    - England - Winchester - Winchester Cathedral - Interiors, Lantern Slides-9 (Box L 12)
    - England - Windsor Castle, Lantern Slides-11 (Box L 13)
    - France - Amiens - Amiens Cathedral, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 17)
    - France - Arles - Roman Theater and Arena, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 17)
    - France - Arles - Saint Trophime Cathedral, Lantern Slides-13 (Box L 17)
    - France - Avignon, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 17)
    - France - Avignon - Palace of the Popes, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 17)
    - France - Bourges - Bourges Cathedral, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 17)
    - France - Chantilly - Chateau, Lantern Slides-8 (Box L 17)
    - France - Chartres - Cathedral at Chartres, Lantern Slides-9 (Box L 17)
    - France - Compiegne Chateau, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 19)
    - France - Fontainebleau - Palace and Grounds, Lantern Slides-9 (Box L 19)
    - France - Lisieux - 16th century House, Lantern Slides-6 (Box L 18)
    - France - Nimes - Arena, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 18)
    - France - Nimes - La Maison Carree, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 18)
    - France - Nimes - Railroad Bridge, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 18)
    - France - Paris - Bridges, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 22)
    - France - Paris - Champs - Elysees, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 22)
    - France - Paris - Cluny Museum, Lantern Slides-7 (Box L 22)
    - France - Paris - Cluny Museum - Unicorn Tapestries, Lantern Slides-5. 1 cracked glass (Box L 21)
    - France - Paris - Gardens, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 22)
    - France - Paris - Luxembourg Gardens, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 19)
    - France - Paris - Notre Dame - Details, Lantern Slides-14 (Box L 21)
    - France - Paris - Notre Dame - Exteriors, Lantern Slides-11 (Box L 21)
    - France - Paris - Notre Dame - Interiors, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 21)
    - France - Paris - Palaces and Civic Buildings, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 22)
    - France - Paris - People, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 22)
    - France - Paris - Public squares and Gardens, Lantern Slides-9 (Box L 22)
    - France - Paris - La Rochefoucauld Unicorn Tapestries, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 21)
    - France - Paris - Saint Etienne-du-Mond, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 21)
    - France - Paris - Sainte Chapelle, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 21)
    - France - Paris - Tuileries Gardens and Arc de Triomphe, Lantern Slides-8 (Box L 22)
    - France - Pierrefonds Castle, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 18)
    - France - Reims - Civic Buildings before and after WWI, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 23)
    - France - Reims - Reims Cathedral - Details - After WWI, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 23)
    - France - Reims - Reims Cathedral - Details - Before WWI, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 23)
    - France - Reims - Reims Cathedral - Exteriors - After WWI, Lantern Slides-6 (Box L 23)
    - France - Reims - Reims Cathedral - Exteriors - Before, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 23)
    - France - Reims - Reims Cathedral - Interiors - After WWI, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 23)
    - France - Reims - Reims Cathedral - Interiors - Before, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 23)
    - France - Reims - Reims Cathedral - Reconstruction, Lantern Slides-6 (Box L 18)
    - France - Rouen, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 18)
    - France - Rouen - Rouen Cathedral, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 18)
    - France - Saint-Gilles Church, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 18)
    - France - Sens - Sens Cathedral, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 18)
    - France - Soissons - before and After WWI, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 23)
    - France - Versailles - Chapel, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 19)
    - France - Versailles - Facades, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 19)
    - France - Versailles - Gardens - Fountains, Lantern Slides-12 (Box L 20)
    - France - Versailles - Gardens - Orangerie, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 20)
    - France - Versailles - General Views, Lantern Slides-6 (Box L 19)
    - France - Versailles - Grand Trianon, Lantern Slides-6 (Box L 20)
    - France - Versailles - Interiors, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 19)
    - France - Versailles - Interiors - Gallery of Battles, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 19)
    - France - Versailles - Interiors - Gallery of Mirrors, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 19)
    - France - Versailles - Le Hameau, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 20)
    - France - Versailles - Little Trianon, Lantern Slides-9 (Box L 20)
    - France - Vezelay - Basilica de la Madeleine, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 18)
    - Fuji - Landscapes, Lantern Slides-14 (Box L 4)
    - Group Portraits - Children - Boys and Beaver, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 36)
    - Japan - Kamakura, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 4)
    - Japan - Koyasan, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 4)
    - Japan - Koyasan - Kongo - Buji Temple, Lantern Slides-7 (Box L 4)
    - Japan - Koyasan - Shojo-Shinin Temple, Lantern Slides-9 (Box L 4)
    - Japan - Kyoto, Lantern Slides-94 total (Box L 5)
    - Japan - Kyoto, Lantern Slides-94 total (Box L 6)
    - Japan - Marriage Ceremony, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 2)
    - Japan - Matsushima Bay, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 3)
    - Japan - Nara - Big Bell, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 4)
    - Japan - Nara - Daibutsu Temple, Lantern Slides-7 (Box L 4)
    - Japan - Nara - Dear Park, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 4)
    - Japan - Nara - Horyuji Temple, Lantern Slides-8, 1 with cracked glass (Box L 4)
    - Japan - Nara - Kasuga - Shinto Shrine, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 4)
    - Japan - Nikko - Iyeyasu Temple, Lantern Slides-69 total (Box L 1)
    - Japan - Nikko - Iyeyasu Temple, Lantern Slides-69 total (Box L 2)
    - Japan - Scenes and People, Lantern Slides-43 (Box L 3)
    - Japan - Unidentified, Lantern Slides-16 (Box L 2)
    - JDR JR - Philanthropies - Riverside Church, Lantern Slides-14 (Box L 36)
    - Korea, Latern Slides-4 (Box L 6)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Grounds and Buildings, Dedication, Lantern Slides-25 (Box L 9)
    - Peking Union Medical College - Informals with JDR JR, Latern Slides-9 (Box L 9)
    - Tokyo - Scenes, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 3)
    - Travel - Bethlehem, Lantern Slides-11 total (Box L 27)
    - Travel - Bethlehem, Lantern Slides-11 total (Box L 31)
    - Travel - Egypt - Abu Simbel, Lantern Slides-23 (Box L 39)
    - Travel - Egypt - Abydos, Lantern Slides-39 (Box L 41)
    - Travel - Egypt - Assuan, Lantern Slides-7 (Box L 37)
    - Travel - Egypt - Cairo, Lantern Slides (Box L 38)
    - Travel - Egypt - Cairo, Lantern Slides (Box L 41)
    - Travel - Egypt - Cairo, Lantern Slides (Box L 42)
    - Travel - Egypt - Dendra, Lantern Slides-21 (Box L 39)
    - Travel - Egypt - Edfu, Lantern Slides-16 (Box L 40)
    - Travel - Egypt - Komobo, Lantern Slides-23 (Box L 28)
    - Travel - Egypt - Luxor, Lantern Slides-34 (Box L 40)
    - Travel - Egypt - Philae, Lantern Slides-21 (Box L 28)
    - Travel - Egypt - Sakkara, Lantern Slides-33 (Box L 37)
    - Travel - Holy Land - Miscellaneous, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 28)
    - Travel - Italy, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 30)
    - Travel - Italy - Florence, Lantern Slides-45 (Box L 30)
    - Travel - Italy - Lucca, Lantern Slides-17 (Box L 29)
    - Travel - Italy - Naples, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 30)
    - Travel - Italy - Syrcause, Lantern Slides-29 (Box L 29)
    - Travel - Jerusalem, Lantern Slides-35 total (Box L 28)
    - Travel - Jerusalem, Lantern Slides-35 total (Box L 31)
    - Travel - Montana Camping Trip, Lantern Slides-13 (Box L 34)
    - Travel - Montana Camping Trip - Glacier Park, Lantern Slides-52 total (Box L 33)
    - Travel - Montana Camping Trip - Glacier Park, Lantern Slides-52 total (Box L 34)
    - Travel - Monte Carlo, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 29)
    - Travel - Tiberias, Lantern Slides-3 (Box L 31)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1924 - Frijoles Canyon, Lantern Slides-8 (Box L 32)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1924 - Grand Canyon, Lantern Slides-8 (Box L 32)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1924 - Hopi Indians, Lantern Slides-16 (Box L 35)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1924 - Mesa Verde Park, Lantern Slides-18 (Box L 34)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1924 - Santa Fe, Lantern Slides-8 (Box L 35)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1924 - Sequoia Trees, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 35)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1924 - Taos, NM, Lantern Slides-1 (Box L 35)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1924 - Yellowstone National, Lantern Slides-15 (Box L 34)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1926 - California Sequoias, Lantern Slides-8 (Box L 35)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1926 - Crater Lake, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 32)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1926 - Mt Hood, Lantern Slides-16 (Box L 32)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1926 - Ojai, CA, Lantern Slides-5 (Box L 36)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1926 - Santa Fe, NM, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 35)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1926 - Tesuque, NM, Lantern Slides-2 (Box L 35)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1926 - Teton Mountains, Lantern Slides-14 (Box L 32)
    - Travel - Western Trip 1926 - Yosemite Valley, Lantern Slides-4 (Box L 36)
    - JDR JR - Illuminated Manuscripts, 52 slides (Box L 43)